Previously on The Chi...
-What happened to your book?
-Things got busy.
You need to leave Nuck
alone and focus on yourself.
Joining the military
does make life easier.
I mean. it's better
than student loans.
Aha. but that's where
scholarships come in.
Alicia pulled mine.
I'll talk to her.
Man. no. I need to
focus on my book anyway.
You want me to attend
my own funeral?
It's not a funeral.
It's more like a
celebration of life.
Just want to thank you
all for coming out.
As you know. this has been a
real difficult time for us.
Really appreciate
you all showing up.
loving on my Jada here.
When I think about my
mama. I can't imagine...
I want you and Kiesha and
your babies to survive.
What are you talking about?
It's too dangerous here.
I want y'all to leave Chicago.
Ma. this city is all I know.
Oh. shit.
-What?
-My water just broke.
I'm gonna get you
to the hospital.
and everything's
gonna be all right.
You trust me?
This is Reg's girlfriend.
If you can help me get
to her. I can to Reg.
I can't bring your son back.
but I can deliver his true
killer to your doorstep.
What's his girl's name?
Candice. She works
at a mobile store.
I love taking young women
like you under my wing.
You need a big
house. luxury car.
-Who you texting?
-My new mentor.
Who mentoring you?
Some lady came
into the shop today
and said she wants to
take me under her wing.
What's she like?
Royal. rich.
She don't need
nothing from nobody.
and she even has an assistant.
-What's her name?
-Terri.
She game me her card.
Keep the car running.
I'll be in and out.
Come here.
♪ Dramatic music ♪
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
♪ Jazz music ♪
They say when one thing dies.
something new is born.
Death is a part of life.
As soon as we're born.
our path to death begins.
Some of us meet our maker
sooner than we should.
No matter when death
comes. we're never ready.
Nothing can prepare us.
It just comes at us.
When we're minding
our own business.
when everything is
going well. then boom...
...you're gone...
just like that.
I fucked up.
What's going on?
-They got Reg.
-Who got Reg?
The cops.
What the fuck y'all do?
Look. he said he wanted
to rob this house.
and he wanted me
to wait in the car.
Why are you niggas so dumb?
What'd I do?
Look. did he have a gun on him?
No.
-You sure?
-I think so.
All right. 'cause
breaking and entering
is not as bad as armed robbery.
Well. can you help
me get him out?
All right. text me where
he keep his stash at
and come get me.
Okay. bet. I'm
texting you right now.
All right.
Fuck.
You know the
hospital's 45 minutes
in the other direction?
I need my bag. I packed it.
Ooh.
See. this is why we need
to be in the car right now.
This is not my first
time at the rodeo.
We got time. Trust me.
Do you know how long it
takes for a baby to drop?
-No.
-Hours.
Some people say in order
to live a new life.
your old one has to die.
Hey. you good?
You had a bad dream?
-It's time.
-Time for what?
-Oh. shit!
-Just breathe.
I'm supposed to be
saying that to you.
-Get the birthing pool.
-Okay. I'm on it.
-Oh. shit.
-Stay calm.
How you calming me down
when you the one
that's giving birth?
I like a calm labor.
I've never been there
for the labor part.
There's a first
time for everything.
I've learned to
embrace my trials...
as well as my triumphs.
I've done things I wish
I could take back. but...
I can't turn back
the hands of time.
All I can do is surrender
and try to survive.
I wonder if I'll ever
get to just enjoy
the world around me.
We'll see.
Until then. this is my story...
for better and for worse.
♪ Dramatic jazz music ♪
♪ Aggressive hip-hop music ♪
What the fuck?
-Get the fuck out.
-Who the fuck is this?
Don't you worry about it.
You could have just told
me you had another bitch.
She ain't mine.
Get your ass out of here.
Hey. give me a minute.
Put the gun down. all right?
Did you kill Douda?
Why do you care? You ain't
even love him like that no way.
I found a letter he wrote me.
He said that if
anybody killed him.
then I'm supposed to kill them.
-Is that right?
-Yeah. that's right.
-Was it you?
-No.
It was Alicia.
You lying.
She hated his ass.
and you know it.
Bianca owed Alicia
a favor. all right?
She got him to the cigar lounge.
And when he got there.
Alicia was waiting on him.
I ain't never trust that bitch.
Which one?
Both of them.
What was that all about?
Get in the room. I'll
be there in a minute.
How'd she get by you?
I fell asleep with
my headphones on.
-Nigga. are you dumb?
-No.
I ain't want to hear you
and your girl fucking.
You are the difference
between me living or dying.
You can't be sleeping
on the fucking job.
♪ Ominous music ♪
♪ Dramatic music ♪
Come on. it has to be in here.
What are you looking for?
I really want a picture of Rob
with me when I have the baby.
When's the last time you saw it?
-I don't know.
-Think.
Oh!
Oh. I can't.
Okay. okay. Um. I'll...
I'll look around.
Oh. thank you.
Ooh...
Congratulations.
You too.
I won't celebrate
till Nuck's dead.
Good luck with that.
Excuse me?
All I can do is
look the other way
if he comes up missing.
You should deliver
him to my doorstep.
If I participate in getting
an informant killed.
it could cost me my job.
And trading one prisoner
for another won't?
My son is innocent.
So was mine.
Is this it?
Oh. thank God.
Oh. my God.
Now. can we please
get in the car
and get to the hospital?
-Yes.
-Come on.
-Ooh. Ooh.
-Just breathe.
When is Lindsey getting here?
She on her way.
Oh. wow.
This is dope.
It looks like a spa in here.
I love a calm birthing ceremony.
Y'all don't need to be here.
y'all can sit on the porch.
Emmett. you're too loud.
My bad. I was just
trying to clear the aura
before the baby get here.
You coming out.
baby. You coming out.
Ooh.
You want to go to the hospital?
No.
♪ Somber music ♪
What do you want me to do?
Just...
I just want to be here.
Okay.
Should... should I call Emmett?
Oh.
Hello?
-Emmett?
-Nah. it's Damien.
Put Emmett on the phone.
Uh. Emmett's a little
preoccupied at the moment.
Look. this is serious.
Yeah. so is this.
It's time.
Wait. how'd you know?
How'd I... Wait. boy. what
are you talking about?
Kiesha's having the baby.
Oh. shit.
What were you talking about?
Jada. she's. uh...
she's making her transition.
What? No. she can't.
-She has to meet the baby.
-Damien. I need my phone back.
Dad. do you want
me to tell Emmett?
Tell me what?
No. don't tell him nothing.
Y'all focus on the baby.
I don't know.
Look. just do as I say.
I'll figure it out.
-Was you looking out?
-Yeah.
And you ain't see
nobody watching us?
No.
Then how the cops pull
up on me that fast?
Probably caught you
on the Ring camera.
This place ain't
have one of those.
I think it was me.
You the rat?
No. but I think
that rich lady is.
See. this is why I don't want
you to be talking to nobody.
Look. I shouldn't have text her.
-What did you say?
-I told her I was scared.
Why the fuck would you do that?
-I'm handling this.
-Apparently not.
What this rich lady look like?
She was older. pretty.
She had a blowout. and
she had an assistant.
I remember that.
-That sound like Shaad bitch.
-Who?
I don't know her name.
but I remember him telling me
he was living with a rich lady.
Q's sister.
That's the bitch that
tried to kill me.
Oh. shit.
Keith let's go.
-What you about to do?
-Get my lick back.
It's our decisions
that define our faith.
Amen.
Isaiah 30:21 states.
"God's voice of
guidance can be heard
in every direction."
-Yeah.
-Amen.
"Each path can grow faith
and show the next step to take."
Yeah.
Now. what that says to me is.
when it's time to walk...
-Uh-huh.
-...you better walk.
Amen.
Stagnation is not faith.
And I know it can be
scary. because sometimes
you may not even see
where you're going
or understand how you got there.
But when your faith says...
it's time to take
another step...
trust God is guiding you.
Amen.
But first you must move.
-Amen?
-Amen.
Amen.
Yeah. Yeah.
Amen
♪ organ music ♪
♪ dramatic jazz music ♪
Hey. girl.
Hey.
How you feeling?
Not good.
Well. you still look
as beautiful as ever.
Oh.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Jada...
...I'm leaving Chicago.
What?
When?
I took what you said at the
last sister circle to heart.
I want to cherish
every day. but...
as long as I'm here. I feel
like I'm gonna be haunted
by my past.
It's time for a change.
You deserve a new chapter.
I'm gonna miss you.
I'm gonna miss you. too.
What's taking so long?
I don't know. It must be
an accident or something.
We don't move any faster.
I'm gonna get out and walk.
No. I can't let you do that.
What you gonna do about it?
I'm gonna have to get
out and walk with you.
-Fuck!
-Just breathe. Just breathe.
Stop telling me to breathe.
-No. we almost there.
-No. we not.
If we ain't go back
for that picture.
we wouldn't be in this
mess in the first place.
So you didn't want me to go back
and get a picture of
my child's dead father
to be with me in spirit
when I give birth?
-Is that what you're saying?
-Of course not.
Then what the fuck
you trying to say?
-This is my fault?
-No. I'm not saying nothing.
I'm just trying to get
us to the damn hospital.
Ooh. shit.
Let me see if I can
find us a detour.
-Yeah. do something. nigga.
-I'm trying. I'm getting over.
-Hey!
-I'm stuck!
You better...
On. bro. you better get
your ass back in the car.
Ooh.
Come on. Kiesha. almost there.
You got it. You got it.
It's... it's... it's...
Come on. baby. it's Game
Six. You Jordan. all right?
Ticker's going. You
coming down the lane.
You about to win
this whole thing.
-Emmett...
-Huh?
-...that ain't helping.
-Okay. okay. my bad. Okay.
Let me get in there with you
-You got this. Kiesha.
-I got you.
We got this. We got this.
I got you.
We got it. We got it.
Come on. baby. you the
strongest woman I know.
The strongest woman I know.
Okay. Kiesha. you got to sit up.
You got to push one more time.
Right there. I'm
right here with you.
Almost there.
Oh.
Boy. what are you doing here?
I told you to focus on the baby.
-They kicked me out.
-Why?
Kiesha said my energy
was too chaotic.
I'm not leaving here
before meeting my grandbaby.
She's right.
This isn't your decision.
It's mine.
I'm going over there.
I don't know.
Trust me. I can
make it over there.
The baby will be here soon.
And I want to be there
when the baby comes.
Um. I can't say no to you.
-I can drive.
-Okay.
All right. help me
get her to the car.
Okay.
Oh.
♪ Life is ♪
♪ Stages and phases ♪
♪ Face it ♪
♪ The wind. it brings changes ♪
♪ We begin ♪
♪ But we envy patience ♪
Ooh.
Hurry up. I need to...
Wait.
Okay. you're doing great.
Kiesha. doing great.
-It's fourth quarter. baby.
-Emmett.
Right. Right. My bad.
Okay. time to push again.
Ooh. Oh.
♪ You just got to breathe ♪
Ooh. Ooh.
Okay. just breathe. You got it.
You got this. You got...
We better not be stuck.
Come on!
♪ To the top. to the top ♪
Now we step into
the editing process.
That is the process where we
go through the book together.
make some tweaks and
some actual edits.
and ideate about what it would
take to make it stronger.
The goal is to make a
seminal piece of work
that will last forever.
So I still got more work to do?
You goddamn right.
You got to keep pushing
until it's timeless.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
Now. my first suggestion
to you as your editor...
think of this book
as volume one.
Why?
Well. you've clearly
lived a lot of life.
but you are still young.
I'm curious about what
your 20s teach you.
and your 30s are gonna be crazy.
I'm not thinking about
my 20s or my 30s.
I just want to make
it through tomorrow.
That's no way to live. son.
With all due respect...
I'm not your son.
I know you aren't. I. um...
But. uh. having you
around has. uh...
it's helped me heal a wound
I didn't know how to tend to.
-I'm sorry.
-No. no. you don't have to be.
No. you've done a lot for me.
It means a lot
that you even think
of me like a son.
I'm honored.
I'm just not good with
bonding with folks.
Well. I read your
book. I can see why.
Hey.
Just... it's all here. man.
How long does the
editing process take?
Uh. as long as it takes.
I had a feeling you
was gonna say that.
Yet you still asked.
You know what? Um...
I think. uh. you
might like this.
Hmm.
You were good today.
It's always nice to
have your approval.
I've never seen
this side of you.
Ah.
There are a lot of things
you don't know about
me. little girl.
♪ Soft music ♪
Hey.
-See you at home. yeah?
-Mm-hmm.
I want us to be a family again.
Well. I think it would
be easier to do that
if we all lived
under the same roof.
Are you asking me
to move in with you?
-Are you ready for that?
-Yes.
I've missed you.
If we're gonna do this.
we need to establish
some ground rules.
That's only fair.
You can come and
go as you please.
but I need to know where you're
going and when you'll be back.
I can do that.
And Kenya's gonna be here
for at least another year
until she gets on her feet.
I look forward to spending
more time with her and Miles.
I have a feeling her and Papa
are gonna get back together.
Yeah. I can see it.
too. He's a good kid.
Yeah. He's sweet.
I have some ground rules. too.
Oh. what rules you got?
I don't think we should sleep
in the same bed for a while.
Well. that is new for you.
This time has to be different.
I agree.
It looks like y'all
stuck between floors.
No shit. Sherlock! Ooh.
We're moving as
fast as we can.
Man. she's about
to deliver a baby.
I really need y'all to move.
Have you ever delivered
a baby before?
No.
If this takes too long.
I'll put the doctor
on the phone.
so they can walk you through.
I'm not having my baby
on a fucking elevator.
Ma'am. you might
not have a choice.
Man. just get the
doctor on the phone
and please try to hurry up.
Get us out of here
as fast as you can.
-Just breathe.
-Ooh.
-Here come another one. Ooh!
-No. no. no.
The baby's coming.
-Huh? Huh?
-I see the head.
You got this. You got it.
You got it. You got it.
-I need to push!
-Are you sure?
Yes!
-Victor. is it?
-Yes.
I need you to be in
position to catch the baby.
Oh.
Tiffany. I need you
to take a deep breath
and push down.
Aah!
Oh. shit. oh. shit. he...
he's coming. he's coming.
Again!
Oh!
Oh.
♪ Soft music ♪
It's a girl.
Just one more.
One more push. Tiffany.
I promise. you got
this. You got this.
Oh! Yes. yes.
Oh. my God. I'm sorry.
Baby's here. He's here.
The baby's here.
He's here. He's here.
He's here. Your
baby boy is here.
He's here.
I love you. Kiesha.
I love you. too. Emmett.
Look. Rob is right here with us.
He's right here with us.
He's beautiful.
-We're moving. We're moving.
-Oh. Thank God.
Okay.
-Are you the father?
-No. no. no. I'm not.
-Come with me.
-Okay.
You got it. You did so good.
Okay. okay.
You did great. You did great.
♪ You were meant for me ♪
♪ No one else could come ♪
♪ Between this love
♪ I know ♪
Okay. right here.
Okay.
♪ You and me. it seems ♪
♪ Never have a problem ♪
♪ We can't overcome ♪
Oh.
It's okay.
She's perfect.
What's her name?
Jada.
♪ Loving you ♪
♪ Has made me feel so fine ♪
We love you. Ma.
Oh.
I love y'all. too.
♪ Jazz music ♪
Mm.
Her name ain't no damn Terri.
It's Alicia.
She set us up.
Damn. can't trust nobody.
Bae. text her and tell
her to meet you somewhere.
Act like it's an emergency.
♪ Dramatic music ♪
I told you.
You can't trust nobody.
Go keep her occupied.
What you about to do?
I'm gonna go in there
and see if she got
anything worth taking.
Keith going with you?
Hell. no. I'm not going
back to jail for nobody.
I don't even hear y'all
talking right now.
Man. go take her to go
meet up with that bitch.
I'm gonna have
Hannibal come scoop me.
Text him the addy.
Have him meet me
here in 15 minutes.
-All right. babe.
-All right.
I'll be back.
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Unh. what you gonna
do when it's go time? ♪
♪ Uh-huh. uh-huh ♪
♪ What you gonna do
when it's go time? ♪
♪ Unh. it's go time ♪
♪ Yeah. it's time to take over ♪
♪ Finish line. run it
up until it's over ♪
♪ Yeah. I been through a lot ♪
♪ That's why my
heart is way colder ♪
♪ Yeah. gotta keep
your head on a swivel ♪
♪ Look over your shoulder ♪
♪ Yeah. 'cause they outside.
and they wanna take you out ♪
♪ But I can't let them ♪
♪ Gotta show 'em
what I'm about ♪
♪ Gotta find a different route ♪
♪ Paper trail. I'm
on a paper trail ♪
♪ Paper chase. I'm
trying to run it up ♪
♪ I come in fresh.
I'm running this ♪
♪ Unh. what you gonna
do when it's go time? ♪
♪ Huh? Yeah. what you gonna
♪ Soft R&B music ♪
I never got a
chance to thank you.
For what?
For introducing me to
Professor Gardner...
...for believing in me.
So what did you think?
I think it's really good.
-Word?
-You're talented.
I've always known that.
I love you.
I love you. too.
Then move in with me.
Your brother not gonna
let me live here.
-I'm getting my own place.
-Since when?
-I saved up some money.
-You told your brother yet?
No. I wanted to tell you first.
Nae. he not gonna like
you living on your own.
He don't have a choice.
and the house he's
staying in is mine.
He's lucky I'm letting him
and his new wife stay here.
So you the big boss now. huh?
I just want to
start a new chapter.
I want a life of my own.
-So do I.
-Then come be with me.
Nuck almost died the
other day 'cause of me.
Keeping him alive should
not be your responsibility.
It's my job to protect him.
And whose job is
it to protect you?
I adore you. Kiesha.
I'm so glad you tough on Emmett.
Sorry.
Mm-mm. don't be.
Can't be a pushover.
You have to stand
up for yourself.
Never forget the sound
of your own voice.
I won't.
I tucked away some
money for you...
to start your own home school.
Thank you.
I'm just glad you helping
Emmett fulfill his dreams.
But don't forget
to follow your own.
♪ Dramatic jazz music ♪
Oh. shit.
What was so urgent
that it couldn't wait?
I want to get away.
-From what?
-My boyfriend.
-Did he hurt you?
-No.
But I think he will if
I don't do what he says.
Bring him to me.
and I'll make sure he never
lays a hand on you again.
What are you planning on doing?
I can make people go away.
I bet.
Just think of me
as your protector.
You look more like
predator to me.
and I guess I look like prey.
♪ Dramatic violin music ♪
♪ Upbeat percussion music ♪
♪ I don't really be chasing ♪
♪ All these silly
hos like you do ♪
♪ Friend nigga like you do ♪
♪ At nigga like you do ♪
♪ Brand nigga like you do ♪
♪ Like nigga like you do ♪
♪ I don't really be chasing
all these silly hos ♪
♪ Like you do ♪
♪ Friend nigga like you do ♪
♪ At nigga like you do ♪
♪ Brand nigga like you do ♪
♪ Like nigga like you do ♪
-Hey.
-We've been robbed.
Oh. shit. Are you okay?
I'm fine.
-Fuck.
-Where are you?
My water broke. and I had
to rush to the hospital.
I had the baby.
Oh. my gosh.
How is he?
Mm. he's perfect.
I knew he would be.
I'll be right there.
Maybe Victor should come by.
No. no. no. I'm coming to you.
Jesus Christ.
What's his name?
Rob Junior.
Oh.
You've made me so happy.
He can't wait to meet you.
I'll be right there.
Okay.
Everything okay?
Somebody robbed our house.
What the fuck? You want
me to go over there?
-No. Alicia's on her way now.
-Oh.
Where's Shaad?
She gave him the night off.
There's always some shit.
What the fuck are
you doing here?
I know you killed Douda.
And who told you that... Nuck?
As a matter of fact. he did.
Well. he's lying.
I watched him do it
with my own eyes.
Really?
Because he said that you
used Bianca to do it.
That was the plan.
So it was premeditated.
He killed my brother.
and I wanted revenge.
Well. so do I.
♪ Ominous music ♪
I don't know why you want
me to leave Chicago so bad.
It's not safe here.
I don't know if
it's safe anywhere.
I just want to know
that you and your family
gonna be okay.
I'll protect them.
And if men like me
keep leaving Chicago.
I don't know what
this city will become.
I respect your decision.
Mm.
-You okay?
-Mm.
♪ Somber music ♪
Mm.
♪ Dramatic music ♪
J?
♪ Callie Day's
"Hear My Prayer" ♪
♪ When my work ♪
♪ On Earth ♪
♪ Is done ♪
♪ And You ♪
♪ Come ♪
♪ To take me ♪
♪ Home ♪
♪ Just ♪
♪ To know ♪
♪ That I am bound ♪
♪ For ♪
♪ Glory ♪
♪ And to hear ♪
♪ You say ♪
♪ "Well done" ♪
It's a beautiful morning.
Yes. it is.
I wish I didn't
have to work today.
Please. you know how many
folks out of work right now?
You better be
grateful for this job.
You right. I need
to get my ass up.
Excuse me.
So I was thinking...
maybe I host you tonight.
Oh.
Well. I can't wait.
But tell me. though.
are you a. um...
shoes-on or a shoes-off
type of house?
I don't wear shoes in the house.
Well. I'll make sure I wear
some sensible socks. then.
Well. I have some
slides if you need them.
♪ Light jazz music ♪
Hmm.
Victor.
Hmm?
What's up?
Did Alicia come by last night?
I don't know.
If she did. she would
have come to my room.
Of course.
I haven't heard from her.
Alicia?
Alicia!
Oh. shit. Oh.
Oh. Oh. shit.
♪ Ominous music ♪
Oh. shit.
This Shaad right here.
Yo. where you at. man?
Tiff had the baby.
I need you to get to
Alicia's house right now.
-What's going on?
-I can't say.
Just get here.
Now!
I got to go.
-What's going on?
-I don't know.
What you mean you don't know?
I'll be right back.
You can't just leave me
here and not say shit.
Look. let me just go
see what's going on.
and I'll call you. I promise.
Okay.
Just breathe.
♪ Dramatic hip-hop music ♪
♪ When we pull up. we gonna
slaughter with the gang ♪
♪ And we talkin'... ♪
So I guess you was
the rat after all.
Not on purpose.
No more talking to
strangers from now on.
Yeah. I'm chillin'.
Enjoy your earnings.
I put mine to the side.
Smart man.
Yeah. me too.
Oh. I want to go to Tulum.
Bae. we can't leave the
country... I'm out on bail.
-We got to lay low.
-For how long?
Just till the cops fall back.
Oh. my gosh.
-You so motherfucking sexy.
-Mmm.
Thanks. baby.
Alicia's dead.
Did you do it?
No. she was dead
when I got there.
Why'd you go over there?
Tiff told me
somebody robbed 'em.
Wha...
Who would want to kill Alicia?
I don't know.
♪ Now my brother grown ♪
♪ I left home for the
dream. now my cousin gone ♪
♪ Ominous music ♪
What the fuck?
I-I-I don't know
what happened. man.
I-I-I walked in here.
a-and the place was a mess.
and she was lying
dead on the floor.
Jesus.
Come on. man. we can't leave
her on the floor like this.
No. we can't touch
the body. bro.
-Nigga. we ain't kill her.
-So?
Look. man. I'm moving
her over to this couch
whether you help me or not.
-Come on!
-Fuck it. bro.
Just... look. man. grab
her right here. okay?
-On three. all right?
-Oh. God.
-One. two. three.
-Fuck.
Oh. man.
What the fuck. bro?
Fuck!
I should've been here.
Hey. man. don't blame yourself.
No. I'm gonna blame
myself. It's my fault.
The house is surrounded.
-Come out with your hands up.
-Shit!
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Ooh. ooh. ooh ♪
♪ Ha ha ♪
♪ Steady. are you ready? ♪
♪ What's going on? ♪
-♪ Steady. are you ready? ♪
-♪ Are you ready? ♪
-♪ What's going on? ♪
♪ I'm down. take a look around ♪
♪ What's going down? ♪
-♪ However do you want me ♪
-♪ However ♪
♪ However do you need me ♪
♪ However do you want me ♪
-♪ However do you need me ♪
-♪ However ♪
-♪ However do you want me ♪
-♪ Do you want me ♪
-♪ However do you need me ♪
-♪ Do you need me ♪
♪ However do you want me ♪
♪ However do you need me ♪
♪ However ♪
-♪ Steady. are you ready? ♪
-♪ Are you ready? ♪
♪ What's going on? ♪
♪ Tell me what's going on ♪
♪ Cold. fresh air ♪
♪ Feel the melody
that's in the air ♪
♪ Oh. yeah ♪
♪ I'm down. take a look around ♪
♪ Oh. it's going down ♪
♪ However do you want me ♪
♪ However do you need me ♪
-♪ Oh. yes. yes ♪
-♪ However do you need me ♪
♪ However do you want me ♪
♪ However do you need me ♪
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm